Thomas M. Rivers Papers 1887-1963 Mss.B.R52
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1941-1963; 9.5 linear feet
  - Cantor, Milton (Box 2)
  - Capoor, S P (Box 2)
  - Carlson, A J (Box 2)
  - Carmichael, Leonard (Box 2)
  - Carpenter, C R (Box 2)
  - Carrington, Mrs. T M (Box 2)
  - Carte Blanche (Box 2)
  - Carter, Dick (Box 2)
  - Carter, Harold M (Box 2)
  - Carver, R K (Box 2)
  - Case, James H,Jr. (Box 2)
  - Cather, J Howard, Jr. (Box 2)
  - Cattell, Garrison (Box 2)
  - Cattell, J McKeen (Box 2)
  - Cattell, Jacques (Box 2)
  - Cary, T Nelson (Box 2)
  - Cavara, V (Box 2)
  - CBS Radio (Box 2)
  - Centre International de l'Enfance (Box 2)
  - Central Intelligence Agency (Box 2)
  - Century Association (Box 2)
  - Chance, Oliver (Box 3)
  - Chandler, Asa Crawford (Box 3)
  - Chandler, L R (Box 3)
  - Chapin,A Winfield (Box 3)
  - Chase, Ester (Box 3)
  - Cheever, F S (Box 3)
  - Cheng, Ping-Yao (Box 3)
  - Chesney, Alan M (Box 3)
  - Chicago Heart Association (Box 3)
  - Child, Margaret (Box 3)
  - Childs, Mary Cole (Box 3)
  - Chinard, Francis P (Box 3)
  - [Chopin,] Purnell (Box 3)
  - Chorley, Kenneth (Box 3)
  - Christian, Henry A (Box 3)
  - Christiernin, Charles L (Box 3)
  - Chumakov, Michael P (Box 3)
  - The Churchman (Box 3)
  - Ciba Pharmaceutical Products (Box 3)
  - Citron, David S (Box 3)
  - City College of New York, Alumni Association (Box 3)
  - City of Richmond, Department of Public Health (Box 3)
  - Clark, George A (Box 3)
  - Clark, Marguerite (Box 3)
  - Clark, Paul F (Box 3)
  - Clark, Ralph L (Box 3)
  - Clark, William S (Box 3)
  - Clark, William S: Caring for Disabled Patients (Box 3)
  - Clarke, Hans T (Box 3)
  - Clinchy, Evrett R (Box 3)
  - The Clinical Endocrinology (Japanese) (Box 3)
  - Cluff, Leighton E (Box 3)
  - Clymer, Ray (Box 3)
  - Coburn, Alvin F (Box 3)
  - Cohen, Morris (Box 3)
  - Cohen, Robert (Box 3)
  - Cohen, Seymour (Box 3)
  - Cohn, Alfred E (Box 3)
  - Cohn, E J (Box 3)
  - Cohn, Victor (Box 3)
  - Colby, Everrtt (Box 3)
  - Cole, Rufus (Box 3)
  - Colin, Edward (Box 3)
  - Collins, Betty (Box 3)
  - Collyer, Dan (Box 3)
  - Colonial Esso Touring Service (Box 3)
  - Columbus, Georgia, Department of Public Health (Box 3)
  - Combes, Frank C (Box 3)
  - Combs, Thomas S (Box 3)
  - Commission on University Education in Hospital Administration (Box 3)
  - Commoner, Barry (Box 3)
  - Concklin, Charles Lewis (Box 3)
  - Condon, Edward U (Box 3)
  - Conference on Epidemiology -, 1952 (Box 3)
  - Conference on Experimental Clinical Cancer Chemotherapy, 2nd (Box 3)
  - Conference on Inactivation of Viruses (Box 3)
  - Conference on Tissue Culture (Box 3)
  - Conference on Virus-Host Cell Relationships -, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Congreso Nacional de Medicina, Argentina, 1934 (Box 3)
  - Conklin, Edwin G (Box 3)
  - Conn, Howard F (Box 3)
  - Conroy, James J (Box 3)
  - Cook, Thomas T (Box 3)
  - Thomas Cook and Son (Box 3)
  - Corbin, Kendall B (Box 3)
  - Córdoba, Félix (Box 3)
  - Corn Exchange Bank Trust Company (Box 3)
  - Cornell University (Box 3)
    - Medical College (Box 3)
    - Veterinary College (Box 3)
  - Corner, George W. (Box 3)
  - Corpus Christi, Texas (Box 3)
  - Cotzias, George C. (Box 3)
  - Couche, Anna (Box 3)
  - Council for International Organizations of Medical Sciences (UNESCO) (Box 3)
  - Cowdry, E. V. (Box 3)
  - Cox, F. I. (Box 3)
  - Cox, Floyd (Box 3)
  - Cox, Harvey W. (Box 3)
  - Cox, Herald R. (Box 3)
  - The Cox Family (Box 3)
  - Craig, Winchell McK. (Box 3)
  - Crawford, Hazel (Box 3)
  - Cross, Roland R. (Box 3)
  - Curphey, Theodore J. (Box 3)
  - Current Biography (Box 3)
  - Current Therapy (Box 3)
  - Curtis, Helena (Box 3)
  - Curtis and Belknap, Attorneys (Box 3)
  - Cusack, Peter J. A. (Box 3)
  - Dale, Sir Henry H. (Box 3)
  - Dalldorf, Gilbert (Box 3)
  - Dalldorf, Gilbert. "National Foundation Research" (Box 3)
  - Dalldorf, Dr. and Mrs. Gilbert (Box 3)
  - Dalrymple-Champneys, Sir Weldon (Box 3)
  - Damon Agency, Inc. (Box 3)
  - Dana, Richard H. (Box 3)
  - Dana, W. (Box 3)
  - Darley, Ward (Box 3)
  - Darling, H. Maurice (Box 3)
  - Davila, Alvaro Muñoz (Box 3)
  - Davis, F. A. Company (Box 3)
  - Davis, Hugh P. (Box 3)
  - Davis, Maxine (Box 3)
  - Davison, Wilburt C. (Box 3)
  - Dawood, M. M. (Box 3)
  - Dawson, M. H. (Box 3)
  - Day, Paul L. (Box 3)
  - Day, Richard L. (Box 3)
  - Debevoise, Thomas M. (Box 3)
  - Delafresnaye, J. F. (Box 3)
  - de la Rivière, R. Dujarrie (Box 3)
  - Delatour, Beekman J. (Box 3)
  - Delbruck, Max (Box 3)
  - Demerec, Milislav (Box 3)
  - Denton, Eugene (Box 3)
  - Denton, Eugene K. (Box 3)
  - De Paul University. Science Library (Box 3)
  - Dern, Emil R. (Box 3)
  - Diethelm, Oskar (Box 3)
  - Dietz, David (Box 3)
  - Dignan, Howard (Box 3)
  - Dillehunt, Richard B. (Box 3)
  - Dinamarco, Luiz Arbex (Box 3)
  - Dingle, John Holmes (Box 3)
  - Directory of Directors (Box 3)
  - Doan, Charles A. (Box 3)
  - Dochez, A. R. (Box 3)
  - Dodge, Bernard O. (Box 3)
  - Dole, Vincent P. (Box 3)
  - Donahue, James J. (Box 3)
  - Dooley, Samuel W. (Box 3)
  - Dornan, William J. (Box 3)
  - Dornbush, A. C. (Box 3)
  - Dorsey, Ralph T. (Box 3)
  - Dorst, Stanley (Box 3)
  - Douglas, Archibald, Jr. (Box 3)
  - Down, Harold A. (Box 3)
  - Downs, Wilbur G. (Box 3)
  - Drew, G. M. (Box 3)
  - Drew, Georgina M. (Box 3)
  - Drew, Molly (Box 3)
  - Dreyfuss, F. (Box 3)
  - Druckman, J. J. (Box 3)
  - Drummond, Margaret C. (Box 3)
  - Dubois, Eugene F. (Box 3)
  - Dubois, Peggy M. (Box 3)
  - Dubos, René J. (Box 4)
  - du Bray, Ernest S. (Box 4)
  - Ducas, Dorothy (Box 4)
  - Dulbecco, B. (Box 4)
  - Dupuis-Deltor, Jacques (Box 4)
  - Duran Reynals, Francisco (Box 4)
  - Duran-Reynals, Francisco. Preliminary Studies on Neoplasia in Mice (Box 4)
  - Dulacher, Mrs. Stanley (Box 4)
  - E. P. Dutton and Sons (Box 4)
  - du Vigneaud, Vincent (Box 4)
  - Dziewiatowski, Dominie D. (Box 4)
  - Eager, Benjamin Franklin (Box 4)
  - Edwards, S. John (Box 4)
  - Egan, Margaret (Box 4)
  - Albert Einstein College of Medicine (Box 4)
  - Eisenhower, Milton S. (Box 4)
  - Eisenstark, A. (Box 4)
  - Elberg, Sanford Samuel (Box 4)
  - Elias, N. M. (Box 4)
  - Elliot, R. C. (Box 4)
  - Elliot, Roger C. (Box 4)
  - Ellner, George G. (Box 4)
  - Elman, Robert (Box 4)
  - Elsmith, Dorothy O. (Box 4)
  - Emberger, Meta Riley (Box 4)
  - Emerson, Kendall, Jr. (Box 4)
  - Emerson, Mrs. Kendall, Jr. (Box 4)
  - Emerton, Robert K. (Box 4)
  - Emory, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Emory University (Box 4)
    - Alumni Association (Box 4)
    - Centenial Celebration (Box 4)
    - Office of the President (Box 4)
  - Enders, John F. (Box 4)
  - Epstein, H. David (Box 4)
  - Epstein, Max (Box 4)
  - Erickson, Harold M. (Box 4)
  - Eskwith, Irwin S. (Box 4)
  - Estill, Revel (Box 4)
  - Evans, E. A.,Jr. (Box 4)
  - Evans, Frank A. (Box 4)
  - Everett, Frank G. (Box 4)
  - Eyler, Don L. (Box 4)
  - Faver, Harold K. (Box 4)
  - Fabian, Joe (Box 4)
  - Fabrikant, Jack (Box 4)
  - Farquhar, S. Edward (Box 4)
  - Farr, Lee E. (Box 4)
  - Farrar, F. W. (Box 4)
  - Faselle, Mary Ann (Box 4)
  - Fay, William E. (Box 4)
  - Fenn, Wallace O. (Box 4)
  - Ferris, Deam H. (Box 4)
  - Fink, Frederick (Box 4)
  - First Bancredit Corporation (Box 4)
  - Fishbein, Morris, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Fishbein, Mrs. Morris (Box 4)
  - Fishbein, Dr. and Mrs. Morris (Box 4)
  - Fisher, Bertha (Box 4)
  - Fitz, Reginald (Box 4)
  - FitzPatrick, Mary Edna (Box 4)
  - Flexner (Box 4)
  - Flexner, Abraham (Box 4)
  - Flexner, James Thomas (Box 4)
  - Flexner, Louis B. (Box 4)
  - Flexner, Dr. and Mrs. Louis B. (Box 4)
  - Flexner, Morris (Box 4)
  - Flexner, Simon (Box 4)
  - Flinn, Waldo R. (Box 4)
  - Folch-Pi, Jordi (Box 4)
  - Forbes, Helen (Box 4)
  - Ford, Corey (Box 4)
  - Foreign Exchange Board, Canada (Box 4)
  - Forest Hills Citizens Defense Committee (Box 4)
  - Forkner, Claude E. (Box 4)
  - Fosdick, Raymond (Box 4)
  - Foster, H. R. (Box 4)
  - Foster, L. Fernald (Box 4)
  - Four Freedoms Foundation (Box 4)
  - Francis, Thomas, Jr., 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Frankfurter, Felix (Box 4)
  - Fraser, F. Clarke (Box 4)
  - Fred, E. B. (Box 4)
  - Fredette, Victorien (Box 4)
  - Freer, Arden (Box 4)
  - Freschl, Lorraine (Box 4)
  - Freund, Jules (Box 4)
  - Friedheim, Ernst A. H. (Box 4)
  - Fromm, Eric (Box 4)
  - Frost, Ernest M. (Box 4)
  - Furlan, Oscar A. (Box 4)
  - Furr, George C. (Box 4)
  - Gabrielli, E. R. (Box 4)
  - Gagnon, O. (Box 4)
  - Galanar, Dorothy B. (Box 4)
  - Galdston, Iago (Box 4)
  - Gallardo, E. (Box 4)
  - Gallardo, Eduardo (Box 4)
  - Gallway, Arthur A. (Box 4)
  - Gamper, R. (Box 4)
  - Gard, Sven (Box 4)
  - Gardner, John W. (Box 4)
  - Gardner, Raymond E. (Box 4)
  - Gardner, W. James (Box 4)
  - Garrett, Steve A. (Box 4)
  - Gasser, Herbert S., 5 folders (Box 4)
  - Gates, Frederick L. (Box 4)
  - Gates, Thomas Sovereign (Box 4)
  - Gauld, Ross L. (Box 4)
  - de Goes, Paulo (Box 4)
  - Gebhardt, Louis P. (Box 4)
  - Geffen Dennis H. (Box 4)
  - Geiger, J. C. (Box 4)
  - Genest, Jacques (Box 4)
  - Georgia Warm Springs Foundation (Box 4)
  - German, James L. (Box 4)
  - Gesell, Raymond (Box 4)
  - Gilbert, John M (Box 4)
  - Gillespie, J E O'N (Box 4)
  - Gillet, Stanley A (Box 4)
  - Ginder, David R (Box 4)
  - Ginsburg, Dr. S (Box 4)
  - Ginzberg, Eli (Box 4)
  - Glasser, Melvin A (Box 4)
  - Glenn, Frank (Box 4)
  - Goddard, Calvin H (Box 4)
  - Goebel, Walther Frederick (Box 4)
  - Goldforb, A J (Box 4)
  - Goldsmith, E D (Box 4)
  - Goldwater Memorial Hospital, Research Divisions (Box 4)
  - Goodman, Charles (Box 4)
  - Goodman, E N (Box 4)
  - Goodman, Irving (Box 4)
  - Goodner, Kenneth (Box 4)
  - Goodpasture, Ernest William (Box 4)
  - Goodpasture, Mrs. E W (Box 4)
  - Goodwin, Rutherfoord (Box 4)
  - Goostray, Stella (Box 4)
  - Gordon, Irving (Box 5)
  - Gorgas Hospital Medical Library (Box 5)
  - Gorka, Mrs. Henry J (Box 5)
  - Gorham, L Whittington (Box 5)
  - Gosline, Harold Inman (Box 5)
  - Gotham Service Bureau (Box 5)
  - Gott, Joseph W, 4th. (Box 5)
  - Gradwohl, R B H (Box 5)
  - Grady, Mrs. Hugh A (Box 5)
  - Graef, Irving (Box 5)
  - Gratia, André (Box 5)
    See: Welsch, Maurice.
  - Graub, Milton (Box 5)
  - Graunke, Heinz (Box 5)
  - Graves, Paul D (Box 5)
  - Greeley, Arthur V (Box 5)
  - Greene, Henry Sylvestre Nutting (Box 5)
  - Gregg, Alan (Box 5)
  - Gregg, Lucien (Box 5)
  - Gregg, Ralph (Box 5)
  - Gress, John Hart (Box 5)
  - Gressit, J Linsley (Box 5)
  - Gressitt, Elizabeth (Box 5)
  - Griswold, Erwin N (Box 5)
  - Groyon, Rose Mary (Box 5)
  - Gruenberg, Herbert M (Box 5)
  - Gruenerwald, William (Box 5)
  - Grumbach, A (Box 5)
  - Grund, Bruce (Box 5)
  - Grune and Stratton (Box 5)
  - Gualtieri, Arthur N (Box 5)
  - Guam; Map and Chart (Box 5)
  - Gudakunst, D W (Box 5)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation (Box 5)
  - Gundersen, Gunnar: "Importance of Increased Use of Polio Vaccine." (Box 5)
  - Gustavson, R G (Box 5)
  - Haddon Hall, Atlantic City, N.J. (Box 5)
  - Hagan, William A (Box 5)
  - Hall of Fame for Great Americans (Box 5)
  - Hallaver, C (Box 5)
  - Halpern, Seymour (Box 5)
  - Hamilton, Andrew (Box 5)
  - Hamilton, Paul B (Box 5)
  - Hamman, Louis (Box 5)
  - Hammel, T (Box 5)
  - Hammon, Wm. McD.: Plan to Test Gamma Globulin Against Polio. (Box 5)
  - Hammond, J F (Box 5)
  - Hampton, Dorothy (Box 5)
  - Hanes, Kenneth F (Box 5)
  - Hann, Charles Jr. (Box 5)
  - Hanssen, Frederick C (Box 5)
  - Harington, Charles (Box 5)
  - Harrell, George T (Box 5)
  - Harriman, W Averell (Box 5)
  - Harris, Carl A (Box 5)
  - Harris, Roger (Box 5)
  - Hartman, Frank W (Box 5)
  - Harvey, A McGehee (Box 5)
  - The Harvey Society (Box 5)
  - Hauduroy, P (Box 5)
  - Hawkins, Forrest E (Box 5)
  - Hayes, Samuel P (Box 5)
  - Haynes, Elmer (Box 5)
  - The Dr. E. C. Hazard Hospital (Box 5)
  - Health Research Fund, 4 folders (Box 5)
  - Hedén, C -G (Box 5)
  - Heggie, Robert (Box 5)
  - Heidelberger, Michael, Lectureship Fund (Box 5)
  - Heilbrunn, C V (Box 5)
  - William Heinemann, Ltd. (Box 5)
  - Hektoen Institute for Medical Research (Box 5)
  - Heller, Leo (Box 5)
  - Helsabeck, B A (Box 5)
  - Henderson, David W (Box 5)
  - Henwood, Stanley E (Box 5)
  - Herman, John R (Box 5)
  - Hernandez-Santana, Gilberto (Box 5)
  - Hershey, A D (Box 5)
  - Hertig, Arthur T (Box 5)
  - Hertz Tailors (Box 5)
  - Herzberg, K (Box 5)
  - Herzog, Wolfgang (Box 5)
  - Hess, Julius H (Box 5)
  - Hess, William R (Box 5)
  - Heustis, Albert E (Box 5)
  - Heuyer, Georges (Box 5)
  - Hewitt, R T (Box 5)
  - Heyman, David M (Box 5)
  - Higginbotham, W C (Box 5)
  - Hildebrandt, Berwyn E (Box 5)
  - Hilleboe, Herman E (Box 5)
  - Hilleman, Maurice R (Box 5)
  - Hilleman, Maurice R et al.: " Progress in the Development of...Polio Vaccine." (Box 5)
  - Sidney Hillman Health Center (Box 5)
  - Hinsdale, Ira A (Box 5)
  - Hinsey, Joseph C: "Educating for Tommorrow's Health." (Box 5)
  - Hinterbuchner, Ladislav Paul (Box 5)
  - Hirschboeck, John S (Box 5)
  - Hirst, George K (Box 5)
  - Hodes, Horace L (Box 5)
  - Hodgkinson, Mr. and Mrs. Melvin Greig (Box 5)
  - Hoechstetter, S (Box 5)
  - Hogue, Mary Jane (Box 5)
  - Hollaender, Alexander (Box 5)
  - Hollingsworth, L A (Box 5)
  - Holman, Emilie (Box 5)
  - Holmes, E M, Jr. (Box 5)
  - Holt, Steven H (Box 5)
  - Henry Holt and Company (Box 5)
  - Hon, Jessie (Box 5)
  - Hopkins, J Gardner (Box 5)
  - Horsfall, Frank L (Box 5)
  - Hotel Dennis, Atlantic City (Box 5)
  - Hotel Shoreland (Box 5)
  - House Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee (Box 5)
  - Howe, Howard A (Box 5)
  - Humanitarian Award (Box 5)
  - Hume, Edgar E (Box 5)
  - Humphreys, George H II (Box 5)
  - Humphries, James H (Box 5)
  - Hurst, E W (Box 5)
  - Hutchins, Robert M (Box 5)
  - Imboden, H M (Box 6)
  - Indiana University, Jordan Hall Dedication Committee (Box 6)
  - Infectious Disease Group Dinner (Box 6)
  - Ingle, Dwight J (Box 6)
  - Ingram, Robert L (Box 6)
  - Institute of Inter-American Affairs (Box 6)
  - Institute of Research on Poliomyelitis - Moscow (Box 6)
  - Institute for Social Adjustment (Box 6)
  - International Association of Gerontology (Box 6)
  - International Association of Microbiologists (Box 6)
  - International Conference on Congenital Malformatior (Box 6)
  - International Congress of Comparative Pathology - I (Box 6)
  - International Congress for Microbiology - 4th - Copenhagen, 1947 (Box 6)
  - International Congress for Microbiology - Stockholm, 1958 - (Box 6)
  - International Date Line (Box 6)
  - International Journal of Microbiology... (Box 6)
  - International Medical Congress, Ltd. (Box 6)
  - International Phage Symposium (Box 6)
  - International Poliomyelitis Congress (Box 6)
  - International Poliomyelitis Congress - 2nd - Denmark (Box 6)
  - International Poliomyelitis Congress - 3rd - Rome (Box 6)
  - International Poliomyelitis Congress - 5th - Denmark (Box 6)
  - International Symposium on the Dynamics of Virus Infections. (Box 6)
  - International Symposium on Enzymes (Box 6)
  - Interurban Clinical Club (Box 6)
  - Irvington House (Box 6)
  - Irwin, Monte W (Box 6)
  - Israel Medical Association (Box 6)
  - Ivanovicz, George (Box 6)
  - Jackson, Robert H (Box 6)
  - Jacobson, Joseph (Box 6)
  - Jacobziner, Harold (Box 6)
  - Jafke, Orville (Box 6)
  - Jahr, Herman M (Box 6)
  - Janeway, Charles A (Box 6)
  - Japan International Christian University (Box 6)
  - Japanese and Military Currency (Box 6)
  - Jefferson Medical College (Box 6)
  - Jerusalem Academy of Medicine (Box 6)
  - Jewish Sanitarium and Hospital for Chronic Diseases (Box 6)
  - John-Brooks, R St. (Box 6)
  - Johns Hopkins University (Box 6)
  - Johns Hopkins University, Alumni Records Office (Box 6)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Medicine (Box 6)
  - Johnson, Greene F (Box 6)
  - Jones, Mrs. Harry, Jr. (Box 6)
  - Jones, T Duckett (Box 6)
  - Jones, Thomas Catesby (Box 6)
  - Jones, Virginia (Box 6)
  - Jones, Waldo H (Box 6)
  - Jonesboro Lodge (Masons) (Box 6)
  - Jonniaux, Alfred (Box 6)
  - Jordan, Edward P (Box 6)
  - Joseph, Morris (Box 6)
  - Jost, Theodore A (Box 6)
  - Journal of Immunology (Box 6)
  - Journées médicales de Bruxelles (Box 6)
  - Juley, Peter A and Son (Box 6)
  - Julianelle, Louis A (Box 6)
  - Kallet, Arthur (Box 6)
  - Kahoe, Walter (Box 6)
  - Kajoika, Robert (Box 6)
  - Kandel, Roscoe (Box 6)
  - Kansas City Health Department (Box 6)
  - Kapoor, K C (Box 6)
  - Karas, Jeff (Box 6)
  - Karsner, Howard T (Box 6)
  - Kasuga, Kitoshi (Box 6)
  - Kellogg, George S (Box 6)
  - Kelser, Raymond Alexander (Box 6)
  - Kempe, C Henry (Box 6)
  - Kannedy, Katherine (Box 6)
  - Elizabeth Kenny Institute (Box 6)
  - Kent, Melvin S (Box 6)
  - Kidd, John (Box 6)
  - Kieval, Howard A (Box 6)
  - Kilbourne, Edwin D (Box 6)
  - King, C G (Box 6)
  - King, John (Box 6)
  - King, Richard (Box 6)
  - King-Size Publications, Inc. (Box 6)
  - Kingdon, Carolyn (Box 6)
  - Kinne, Arthur Lyman (Box 6)
  - Kirby, W M (Box 6)
  - Kirman, David (Box 6)
  - Kitselman, Charles H (Box 6)
  - Klechak, Thomas (Box 6)
  - Kline, Marvin L (Box 6)
  - Klingman, Walter O (Box 6)
  - Knecht, Charlotte M (Box 6)
  - Knight, C A (Box 6)
  - Knopf, Alfred A (Box 6)
  - Kobayshi, Rokuzo (Box 6)
  - Kogel, Marcus D (Box 6)
  - Kolb, Larry (Box 6)
  - Kolmer's Vaccine (Box 6)
  - Kordi, A A (Box 6)
  - Korenchevsky, V (Box 6)
  - Korns, Robert F (Box 6)
  - Kramer, Mrs. Lee (Box 6)
  - Kramer, Victor H (Box 6)
  - Krieghbaum, Hillier (Box 6)
  - Krimsky, Isidore (Box 6)
  - Kruif, Paul de (Box 6)
  - Kubie, Lawrence S (Box 6)
  - Kumm, Henry, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Kungl. Lantbrukshögskolan (Box 6)
  - Kunkel, Henry G (Box 6)
  - Kunkel, L O (Box 6)
  - Kurland, Leonard T (Box 6)
  - Kursh, Harry (Box 6)
  - Kutler, William (Box 6)
  - Labby, Daniel H (Box 6)
  - Ladimer, Irving (Box 6)
  - LaGuardia, Fiorella (Box 6)
  - Lake Placid Club (Box 6)
  - Lancefield, Rebecca C (Box 6)
  - Landauer, Kenneth S (Box 6)
  - Harriet Lane Dispensary (Box 6)
  - Lane, R A G (Box 6)
  - Lane, W Kenneth (Box 6)
  - Langmuir, Alexander D (Box 6)
  - Langsam, Walter C (Box 6)
  - Lapsley, Howard G (Box 6)
  - Lasker, Mrs. Albert D (Box 6)
  - Lauffer, Max A (Box 6)
  - Laurence, William L (Box 6)
  - Lauson, Henry D (Box 6)
  - Lavan, John L (Box 6)
  - Lavin, George (Box 6)
  - Lawell, Myra (Box 6)
  - Lawrence, H Sherwood (Box 6)
  - Leaders in American Science (Box 6)
  - Leake, Chauncey D (Box 6)
  - Lebanon Hospital (Box 6)
  - Lefevre, Enrique (Box 6)
  - Legg, J (Box 6)
  - Legion of Merit (Box 6)
  - Leland, R G (Box 6)
  - Lennette, Edwin H (Box 6)
  - Leonidoff, Leon (Box 6)
  - Leopold, Mrs. John J (Box 6)
  - Lépine, Pierre (Box 6)
  - LeShan, Lawrence L (Box 6)
  - Lethbridge, Mary C (Box 6)
  - Levine, S Z (Box 6)
  - Levy, Robert L (Box 6)
  - Lewis, D Sclater (Box 6)
  - Lewis, John R Jr. (Box 6)
  - Lewis, Mildred R (Box 6)
  - Lewis, William Hall, Jr. (Box 6)
  - Li, C P (Box 7)
  - Libenson, Leon (Box 7)
  - Life Magazine (Box 7)
  - Lin, Morris (Box 7)
  - Lind, Vincent E (Box 7)
  - Lindsey, Edna (Box 7)
  - Linsk, Joseph A (Box 7)
  - J. B. Lippincott Company, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Lipton, Murray M (Box 7)
  - Litchfield, Edward H (Box 7)
  - Little, Clarence C (Box 7)
  - Little, Mre. Joseph (Box 7)
  - Littman, M L (Box 7)
  - Liu, Oscar C (Box 7)
  - Locke, A C (Box 7)
  - Lockie, Alice N (Box 7)
  - Loeb, Robert F (Box 7)
  - London Lancet (Box 7)
  - Long, Esmond R (Box 7)
  - Long, Perrin H (Box 7)
  - Longcope, Warfield T (Box 7)
  - Loosli, Clayton G (Box 7)
  - Lorente de No, Rafael (Box 7)
  - Loughlin, Elmer H (Box 7)
  - Lowman, Dr. and Mrs. Charles L (Box 7)
  - Luchi, Robert J. (Box 7)
  - Lucké, Balduin (Box 7)
  - Lull, George F (Box 7)
  - Luria, S E (Box 7)
  - Lwoff, André (Box 7)
  - Lyle-Samuels, Alexander (Box 7)
  - Lynch, Francis W (Box 7)
  - MacArthur, General Dougals Tribute Dinner (Box 7)
  - McCabe, Frank (Box 7)
  - McCahill, William P (Box 7)
  - McCammon, Charles J (Box 7)
  - McCann, William S (Box 7)
  - McCarty, Maclyn (Box 7)
  - McClung, L S (Box 7)
  - McCombs, Robert M (Box 7)
  - McCormack, James E (Box 7)
  - McCrae, F W (Box 7)
  - McCrumb, Fred R, Jr. (Box 7)
  - McDermott, Walsh (Box 7)
  - McDougal, Robert A (Box 7)
  - McEwen, Currier (Box 7)
  - MacFadyen, Douglas Archibald (Box 7)
  - Macfarlan, W J (Box 7)
  - Macfarlane, Marjorie (Box 7)
  - McGinnes, G Foard (Box 7)
  - McGuinness, Aims C (Box 7)
  - M'Gowan, J (Box 7)
  - McGrath, Thomas (Box 7)
  - McGuire, Eleanor E (Box 7)
  - McIntire, Ross T (Box 7)
  - McIntosh, Rustin (Box 7)
  - McKinnon, N E (Box 7)
  - McKusick, Victor A (Box 7)
  - McLean, John M (Box 7)
  - MacLaren, Donald (Box 7)
  - MacLeod, Colin M (Box 7)
  - MacMeekan, Marguerite Hughey (Box 7)
  - The Macmillan Company (Box 7)
  - McMillin, John N (Box 7)
  - McNally, John J (Box 7)
  - McNamee, Mrs. C (Box 7)
  - McQuard, Eleanora O'Neill (Box 7)
  - McQuarrie, Irvine (Box 7)
  - McRae, Floyd W (Box 7)
  - Macrae, John (Box 7)
  - Madsen, Sten (Box 7)
  - Madsen, Thorward (Box 7)
  - Magath, Thomas B (Box 7)
  - Magnuson, Beatrice A (Box 7)
  - Magrassi, Flaviano (Box 7)
  - Mahoney, John F (Box 7)
  - Maier, John (Box 7)
  - Maisel, Albert Q (Box 7)
  - Maisel, Albie (Box 7)
  - Manners, L W (Box 7)
  - Maramorosch, Karl (Box 7)
  - Marcus, Lloyd (Box 7)
  - The John and Mary R Markle Foundation (Box 7)
  - Marks, Robert W (Box 7)
  - Marquette University School of Medicine (Box 7)
  - Marsh, Robert McC (Box 7)
  - Marshak, Alfred (Box 7)
  - Martzloff, Karl H (Box 7)
  - Marvin, Mrs. S Stephen (Box 7)
  - The William J Matheson Commission, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Mathieson, Don R (Box 7)
  - Matthews, Warren B (Box 7)
  - Maurer, Marion (Box 7)
  - Maxcy, Kenneth F (Box 7)
  - Mayer, J de C (Box 7)
  - Mayer, Manfred (Box 7)
  - Mayo, Beverly C (Box 7)
  - Mayo Foundation (Box 7)
  - Measles - Lab Notes/Results, 1931 (Box 7)
  - Medical Arts Publishing Foundation (Box 7)
  - Medical Association of Georgia (Box 7)
  - The Medical Association of the State of Alabama (Box 7)
  - Medical/Case Records, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Medical Communications, Inc. (Box 7)
  - Medical Economics (Box 7)
  - The Medical Letter (Box 7)
  - Medical Preparedness (Box 7)
  - Medical Radio System (Box 7)
  - Medical Research Council (Box 7)
  - Medical Research Council, International Nomenclature Committee (Box 7)
  - Medical Society of the County of New York (Box 7)
  - Medical Society of the State of New York (Box 7)
  - Medical Society of New York; Committee on Public Health and Education (Box 7)
  - Medical World News (Box 7)
  - Mellon Institute of Industrial Research (Box 7)
  - Melnick, Joseph L (Box 7)
  - Melnick, J L: Polio Outbreak at Cornell (Box 7)
  - Melton, W F (Box 7)
  - Menaker, Walter (Box 7)
  - Merrill, George Adams (Box 7)
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance Company (Box 7)
  - Meyer, Karl (Box 7)
  - Meyer, Karl F (Box 7)
  - Michael Reese Hospital (Box 7)
  - Michigan Clinical Institute (Box 7)
  - Michigan Department of Health (Box 7)
  - Michigan Public Health Association (Box 7)
  - Microbiological Associates, Inc. (Box 7)
  - Middlesex Hospital, London (Box 7)
  - Milbank, Jeremiah (Box 7)
  - Miller, Bernard S (Box 8)
  - Miller, Charles Phillip (Box 8)
  - Miller, James R (Box 8)
  - Miller, Robert M (Box 8)
  - Miller, Sydney R (Box 8)
  - The Minneapolis Tribune (Box 8)
  - Mitchell, A Graeme (Box 8)
  - Mitchell, John McK (Box 8)
  - Mitchell, MacNeil (Box 8)
  - Mitchell, Patricia T (Box 8)
  - Mizell, R C (Box 8)
  - Modern Medicine (Box 8)
  - Moe, Henry Allen (Box 8)
  - Moore, Norman S (Box 8)
  - Moore, William F (Box 8)
  - Mooser, H (Box 8)
  - Morgan, Herbert R (Box 8)
  - Morgan, Hugh J (Box 8)
  - Morgan, Marie (Box 8)
  - Mori, Joseph (Box 8)
  - Morrison, Charles C (Box 8)
  - Morrison, Ira R (Box 8)
  - Morshead, Mrs. E C (Box 8)
  - Morton, John Jamieson, Jr. (Box 8)